Can you tilt it down?
All right, perfect.
Okay, Kim, you can get us started.
>> Hey, DJ, welcome back. What What was
last year like
>> recording in progress?
>> Having to sit out all those games
knowing what you were brought here for?
>> It was tough. Uh we worked so hard
during the offseason, trained trained
together, uh all the guys and I day in
day out. came in practice early, did
things after practice, ate together,
played games together, build a
camaraderie, and uh we had a really good
first game and then the second game I
felt like it was um I felt it was it was
I felt kind of sad because I got hurt
and I feel like I was leaving my team,
leaving my guys that we worked hard
together and I wanted to do it with
them. Regardless of the outcome, doing
it with your with with the guys that you
started with always means something. So,
I'm real glad and and honored to be back
in Washington to do it again.
>> And then what you know, you're now
coming in for a new another or different
defender.
What do you think about like Dante Jones
and what are you looking forward to this
year?
>> I'm I'm looking forward um getting back
on the field with my teammates. Um
whatever the the defense is, I feel like
I'll be able to adapt to it. um know
knowing coach and his background, I feel
like I'm very familiar with his defense.
So, um my main thing is just getting
back healthy, getting back on the field,
uh and staying on the field.
>> David Harrison,
>> hey D, congratulations. Um I know
>> I know coming back was something you
really really wanted even throughout
your recovery process. So when you kind
of had those first conversations or knew
those conversations right with the front
office to bring you back kind of just
how did you feel about that potential?
>> You know uh it was an honor uh hearing
those words that they wanted me back. Um
one of the things that I I really wanted
to do was that when they saw me made me
back I was on the right track of of my
healing process getting everything
going. Um, and I just want to be able to
continue healing, continue working out,
continue rehabbing, getting stronger,
getting getting faster, and uh, being
100% so I can get back on the field. I'm
able to help help the team win.
>> And I know during your recovery process,
you were able to spend a good amount of
time around the guys. I know they
benefit from that, but what do you what
do you also get from from being around
the guys during your recovery?
>> Uh, camaraderie. Uh, knowing that you're
not doing anything alone. Uh, when
you're when you're working when when you
are rehabbing from an injury, uh, it's
pretty tough. uh on all aspects,
mentally, physically, emotionally. So,
just um being around guys sometimes
helps break the monotony of rehab. Um
sometimes just looking out the window,
seeing the guys on the fields like, "All
right, cool. Like, I have something to
strive for." Just like seeing even
though you you know it. Um being around
family, being around these guys, it kind
of helped the process um along pretty
smoothly.
>> Thanks, Dri.
>> Thank you,
>> Candy.
Hey Dietrich, welcome back.
>> Hey, thank you. How you doing?
>> Good. Um, so kind of along the lines of
what uh John and David just asked, um,
what has this recovery process been like
for you? Like where are you in the
process?
>> Oh, I'm uh I feel like I'm doing really
really well. Uh, the journey was tough.
Um, it was ups and downs. There was good
days, there was not so good days, but uh
it was something that uh taught me a lot
during this process. uh being present,
um being thankful for where I'm at now
and how far I' I've came. Um taking
every day one step at a time, um seeing
the progressions cuz when you get hurt,
you tend to start over on something. And
sometimes that's the hardest part of
anything, starting all the way over. Um
could barely lift 10 pounds. Now I'm I'm
working out back to the weight that I'm
used to doing now. I'm getting stronger.
So seeing those daily progressions, uh,
they meant a lot to me and, uh, now I'm
progressing to doing more movement,
which is really good.
>> Okay, thank you so much for that. And
then one more from me. Um, have you had
a opportunity to talk to coach Donte
Jones yet? And, you know, if so, or if
not, what have you learned about him?
Um, so far,
>> uh, cool guy. Haven't had any deep
conversations, but we we spoke and he's
a great guy. uh talk to him about his
his uh coaching past, where he came
from, and kind of like his his
philosophy, stuff like that. So, uh just
understanding
understanding uh his his defense and
what he's bringing to to the to the
team.
>> All right. Thank you so much.
>> Thank you,
>> Donna.
>> Hey, Dietrich.
>> Hello. How you doing?
>> Yeah.
Um, what did you learn about yourself
going through this process in getting
back to where you are right now?
>> Uh, resiliency. I'm a lot stronger than
I give myself credit for. Um,
I'm very patient and uh, I have the,
um, ability to still grow. I have room
to still grow. I have areas that I still
need to improve in. And um uh it was it
was a journey. I'll put it that way. It
was a it was it was a good a good
journey um that I I think I learned a
lot from myself, learned a lot from
others around me and um it made me a
better person.
>> And in signing back with the commanders,
why was it so important for you to come
back this year with this team?
>> Well, I felt like there was a lot of
unfinished business last year. uh got
hurt first part in the first two games
of the season and uh I I I started it
with the guys and I I really wanted to
finish it with them. Um these these guys
are great. I built a lot of good good
relationships with these these these
guys. Uh them are my my brothers. We
have group chats. We we we talk. So um
it kind of hurt me to to leave the game
how I did last year. So, I just want to
be able to not only do it with them, go
to war with them, work with them every
single day, but also um uh put good
product on the field so that so that
when we have game days, uh the DC fans,
the the Commanders fans uh are liking
what they see as well. So, that's it.
>> Thanks.
>> No problem.
>> Natalie,
>> hi D. Welcome back.
>> Hey, thank you. No question the defense
is going to look very different come
next week, new pieces brought in. But
when it comes to what you guys were able
to establish last year, the culture, the
chemistry, what are maybe some of your
messages to, you know, those potential
new guys coming in to say, "Hey, this
is, you know, the way things are done
here or what we want to do essentially."
>> Big brotherhood team. Um, I I really
believe you cannot lead people without
knowing them. And that's one thing that
that DQ DQ preaches every single day. Um
he's all about brotherhood, all about
knowing his guys. And then on top of
that, he takes care of the players. So
he we teach hard work, coming in every
single day, doing what is right because
it is right, being present, putting good
product on on the field, uh building
that camaraderie on the field and off
the field. And then through that through
that we're having fun through that we're
learning about each each other. And uh
we're going to we his one of his
favorite sayings is doing hard things
with good people. So if we can continue
uh doing hard things with good people,
it m it makes the work lighter.
>> Awesome. Thank you.
>> No problem.
>> Blake, did you have a question?
>> Yes, I did. Let me get that. Welcome
back, D.
>> Thank you. uh you know last year when
you got hurt you know the the outpouring
of support from your teammates and fans
as well for you to be a new face on the
team. How how special was that for you
considering the circumstances?
>> I mean I I I really appreciate I
appreciate all the the support from the
fans, the support from the team. Um this
is a really great this is a great city
uh great fan base uh that the the
commanders have and um they reached out
to me. that that that that show love and
then just to have the warmth of the
team. Um me being here for a short such
a short time and how much love that I I
received on the field, off the field,
and after the at like throughout the
season was was was good and I knew that
I wasn't doing it by myself, you know.
>> All right. Congratulations.
>> Thank you.
>> Awesome. Thank you, Durch.
>> No problem.
>> Thank you, everyone.